

# **PROFILE**

With a background as a Specialist Soldier, Civil Engineer, Project Portfolio Manager, Business Systems Developer, and Full-Stack Web Developer (in the making), I have the confidence, technical abilities, leadership skills and sheer determination to become a pivotal part in developing most company's into a global powerhouse.

## **CONTACT**

PHONE: +61 433 788 336

WEBSITE: KanesTrades.com

EMAIL: Kane@KanesTrades.com

#### **HOBBIES**

Developing Businesses & Smashing Any Competition

# KANE ROBINSON

**EXECUTIVE TEAM RIGHT-HAND-MAN** 

# **FORMAL EDUCATION**

1999 | COMPLETED YEAR 12 | TER SCORE OF 87 (87TH PERCENTILE)

2004 | ADVANCED DIMPLOMA CIVIL/STRUCTURAL ENGINEERING

2020 | UWA FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# METAGO ENVIRONMENTAL ENGINEERS | ON-SITE ENGINEER 2008–2012

Started as Civil-Design Manager and progressed to Site Engineer. Redesigned companies drafting systems and increased drafting/design efficiency by 500% (1 person could do what it took 5 people to do).

# SUPERDRAFT.COM.AU | OPERATIONS MANAGER

2012-2016

Worked closely with the company's executive team to build the company into Australia's largest residential projects Architectural enterprise.

# VIZ360.COM | OPERATIONS MANAGER

2016-2020

Worked closely with the company's executive team to build the company into Australia's most advanced 3D visualizations enterprise.

# **SKILLS**

